I think we're in a disbelief phase. I've
called it since the bottom that the
ecosystem was due for a run. You know, I
hate beating I hate I actually don't
like coming back to this because there's
a lot of people there why are you still
talking about pulse chain? Listen, I
shut up about this thing for a long
time. I wasn't talking about I ain't
been talking I like Maddie Allen to you
Maddie all in Maddie Allen.
He's those guys are talking about pulse
chain hex every single day. I left it
alone. But when I started to look like
it was ready to do something then I come
back and I start buying. I don't like
doing this but I just have to do it for
the people who sit in the back of the
classroom and say stupid stuff. I
started accumulating hex back here.
Okay? So I'm not just a bag holder. I
kind of double down. Okay? So I can get
bullish. I can get excited. Maybe you
can't because you're down so much. You
didn't buy any when it was down.
Um but this is me and what I'm doing.
Okay?
So hex is looking good. I don't see
anything bearish about it other than
it's went up a lot. It just cut keeps
coming down to when we get red candles
what's going to happen. Before I get
into that huge announcement pulse x is
now on moretokens.com.
Is it me? Maybe it's me. Maybe I'm the
one that's pumping pulse chain because
I'm the only one doing anything.
So we now have more pdi pls plsx.
You can now stake your plsx. For those
of you who don't know what what more
tokens is it's basically a platform that
allows you to lock your tokens up and
keep them away from yourself so you
don't panic sell. Okay? Now I created
this because holding Bitcoin would have
been the best thing. But it's really
hard to hold when you have liquid coins
in your hands. Like you you can just
sell them whenever. So this is a way to
lock up the tokens from yourself and
earn yield. It's basically HEX without
the inflation. So, I can stake some
PulseX here. Let's just do a test for
100,000. Now, what I'm noticing is a lot
of people are doing Pulse. You can see
the APY currently is at 69%.
The balance is growing by 97% in the
past 24 hours. It's pretty cool.
So, you'll see like this guy right here.
He's thought he would stake 30 million
Pulse for 1 day.
Doing it for 1 day
is not going to work. The yield comes
from penalties. [clears throat]
So, a great example, like people will
and people say, "Well, what if nobody
gets penalized?"
Look at how many late stakes. Let me
explain.
When you stake and you claim your stake
early, you get penalized
based on how far along your stake was.
So, if your stake was 50% through,
you get 50% slashed from your your
balance, your stake.
If you're 90% through, you get 10%
slashed from your balance.
If you're 10% through, you get 90%
slashed from your balance. So, the
penalties work like that. And then
there's a 14-day grace period after your
stake ends where you're free to claim
with no penalties. And then after 14
days, you start getting penalized again.
And this goes and this expe-
exponential up to 700 days where you
lose everything. The 700 days. Now, what
we're seeing on more is
people are coming back and claiming
their stakes late. And let's see if we
can find one. There hasn't been one in a
while. Here's one.
This stake right here, they staked for
200 They staked for 122 days, but they
were over 100 days late. So, they got
penalized. Now, what's funny is they
still made a ROI, but they got
penalized. This penalty goes to everyone
still staked.
So, what I do
is I don't do these one day, two days.
You're not going to get anything.
It's a long-term game. What you want to
do is you want to try and capture as
much of this as possible so that you can
get reap the rewards of this.
See, now
being that I staked Now, this isn't a
good wallet because I didn't really do I
just started using this wallet.
But,
you can see that they're starting to
come in.
This has been staked for This is a short
one. I don't have any long ones here.
Here's one started a year ago.
See this one? These are starting to pay
off
cuz it's been a while. This one doesn't
unlock till 2040.
But,
you can see that over time by the time I
get by the time November 11, 2040 rolls
around, probably it's a high chance this
is going to be a high number
because
most people
aren't going to be able to keep up with
it. So, what I want to do is I want to
capture as much of this as possible.
So, when you're doing your stakes,
probably the better idea to do it for a
long time. So, let's do that PulseX
stake. Let's go for
365 days.
And
then you say, "Well, what's the point of
going in now? There's no rush to go in."
It's crazy. I don't know, but the start
of everyone, there's been rewards.
There's been a lot of uh
early end stakes. People just start
crazy. I don't know. So, they're still
There's always rewards.
There has always been rewards.
All right.
And we'll add that to the ladder.
So, yeah, PulseX is now live on
moretokens.com. I think INK will be
next. We'll see.
But,
you can already see on
on the pulse staking, there's already a
stake
that's turned orange. People are already
starting to forget. So, you kind of want
to get out in front of all of this, you
know? Right now, that's looking like
it's about until
November next year, but really
a year.
Most of it's in a year right now on the
pulse one.
And then on p die,
there's been someone building a ladder
all the way out.
So, there's a lot
here. And look, they're already starting
to bleed out. Let's see. Not bleeding,
but I can't even get my mouse on it, but
there it is.
One day past. So, in 14 days, this one
will start getting penalties. And then
when they and eventually [clears throat]
come get it,
they're going to have to pay a penalty.
And the penalty's going to go to all the
people who are staked.
There's also a more buying burn.
This, I think, will start to heat up in
a couple months as well.
And it's funny because more is actually
up more than all of the other tokens on
pulse chain.
So, the biggest gainer on pulse chain
right now is Well, it's not on pulse
chain, but hex on Ethereum
is up like 300%
from this point.
334.
But then you got more on pulse chain
that's up
804%.
So, and that's before
staking.
Like
add another 50% if you I mean, for the
past year, if you've been in it for the
past year.
Add another 54% on top of that. So,
double of that. So, you're really up
like 1,600%.
So,
quietly just over here building,
building, building, building. And I
actually love the direction this is
going because it's so crazy like how
when you put something in motion and
don't put too much thought into it, it
all kind of comes together.
moretokens.com
moretokens
>> [snorts]
>> So, the goal is to have
all if a popular token pops up it will I
I want it to be on moretokens.com and it
just is a self-marketing machine.
Um because [clears throat]
it kind of sells itself. If you really
are really if you're really bullish on
the coin that you're holding
you might want to stake it and lock it
away from yourself
to make sure you can stick around for
the gains.
Because if you're
liquid
it's going to be if it goes starts to go
down, you're going to want to sell it.
If it starts to go up, you're going to
want to sell it.
So, it's kind of a way to keep you
seeing it through.
Um
the yield
that's just a cherry on top. You know,
this is a tool for you to stake your
tokens and lock them up. It's like a
locker. It's not like a yield producing
machine. Although it has been because 50
per 4%
on a capped supply token
is pretty good, you know?
So
let's check out HEX on PulseChain.
Yeah, it's looking good.
Everything's looking good on PulseChain.
That's not to say that it's going to
keep going that way
but man, it's a start.
It's looking Guys, I don't know, man.
Like I'm still seeing a lot of disbelief
on the timeline.
And
rightfully so.
But this is we haven't had a run like
this I
with continuation like since back here.
And even then this move was
not as bullish as the pullback was a lot
further on on this one.
Um
ultimately, though,
what we need to see is when the
PulseChain
starts to roll over,
does it stop rolling over? Or is it just
a repeat of what always happens where
rolls over and it just falls and falls
and falls and falls and falls.
When we roll over,
you know, do we stay in the range?
I like to just see us
trending up.
Pullback,
new high. Pullback, new high.
Um when that stops happening, I'll get
bearish again. But this is bullish.
And the catalysts, I already know it's
it's Richard Heart buying the coins,
man. And it's like
you can sit and be like, "Oh, well,
that's fake. That's
uh you know, and talk down on it." But
or you could just get on the ride.
Maybe just get on the ride.
Um I'm not buying here.
I'm already in. I'm satisfied with what
I got. I'm focused on more and building
that out as a platform
and just pumping my bags, you know,
building and pumping my bags, you know,
building stuff that people can use
that you know,
help.
I'm doing my part, guys.
That's about it. Like I said, PulseX
staking is live.
You want to get in early?
Yeah. But when you get in early, you
want to stake for a while. You don't
want to do these one-day, two-day type
things.
Um
it's not going to really help you much.
It's not going to really do anything.
The full effect is
you know, do maybe doing what this guy
did here. You know, he did a ladder.
Every couple he Every couple Actually,
he's he's doing one every couple hours
actually.
6:18, 6:19, 6:40, you know.
It's cool to see. Hopefully he forgets.
Hopefully he forgets a couple times.
Um
that'll be fun. Just kidding.
That's about it, man. I'll talk to y'all
in the next one.